{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Inground Pool Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46473/":{"taskOID":46473,"originalTaskOID":46473,"setID":1493,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7576,"questionDisplayText":"Type of pool install","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of in ground pool do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11496,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11497,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11498,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Vinyl lined","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl lined","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7576,"questionDisplayText":"Type of pool install","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of in ground pool do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11496,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11497,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11498,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Vinyl lined","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl lined","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11496,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11497,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11498,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Vinyl lined","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl lined","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/46473/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46473,"taskName":"Swimming Pool - In Ground - Build or Install","taskDescription":"Build or Install an In Ground Swimming Pool","xmTaskDescriptor":"Inground Pool Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":4612,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"inground pool ground installation swimming","textMessagingName":"In Ground Pool","rolloverLongDesc":"In-ground concrete, fiberglass and vinyl pool builders.","rolloverShortDesc":"In-ground concrete, fiberglass and vinyl pool builders.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build or Install an In Ground Swimming Pool.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Inground Pool Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Build In-Ground Swimming Pool","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":61,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"In Ground Swimming Pool Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Swimming Pool: In Ground - Build or Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Swimming Pool Project","urlName":"In-Ground-Swimming-Pool-Installation-Build","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Inground Pool Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"inground,pool,ground,installation,swimming","emcCategoryOid":-12070,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1493,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}